Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Printed Ephemera Collection on Trade Unions PE.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- W, 1847-2011; 2 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Merger of Seamen and Dockers with Land and Air Transport Workers, 1953 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Pamphlets and Publications, 1949-1963, undated (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Pamphlets and Publications, 1963-1989, undated (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Pamphlets and Publications: About WFTU, 1965, undated (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Pamphlets and Publications: Apartheid, 1964, undated (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Pamphlets and Publications: Conferences, 1952-1970 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Pamphlets and Publications: Free Trade Unions, 1949 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Pamphlets and Publications: Indochina, 1973-1974 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Pamphlets and Publications: Paris Commune, 1971 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Pamphlets and Publications: Women, 1966 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Pamphlets and Publications: WFTU & The United Nations, 1947-1973 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): Reports, 1945-1949 (Box 48)
  - World Federation of Trade Unions (WFTU): World Federation of Teachers' Unions, 1952 (Box 48)
  - World Trade Union Congress: Congress (Berlin), 1986 (Box 48)
  - World Trade Union Congress: Congress (Moscow), 1961 (Box 48)
  - Writers and Professional Workers' Union of Greater Boston, 1935, 1939 (Box 48)
  - Writers Guild of America, 1978, 1988 (Box 48)
  - Writers Guild of America: Agreements, 1977 (Box 48)
  - Writers Guild of America: Agreements, 1988 (Box 48)
  - Writers Guild of America, East, 1977, undated (Box 48)
  - Writers Guild of America, West, 1977-1978 (Box 48)
- Y, 1948
  - Yiddish Writers' Union, undated (Box 48)
  - Young Artists Guild: Local 65, 1948 (Box 48)